http://www.instrument.com/legal

Skip to main content
Close
Stay up to date
Join our newsletter
Privacy Statement Effective: July 14, 2017Instrument LLC (“Instrument,” “we,” “us,” “our”) is committed to letting you know how we will collect and use your personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement is applicable to your use of the Instrument’s websites (the “Website”). We have established this Privacy Statement to let you know the kinds of information we may gather when you use the Website, why we gather your information, what we use your information for, when we might disclose your information, and how you can manage your information.This Privacy Statement does not apply to information that users may submit to us offline, by email or other electronic file transmission not facilitated by our Website, or to third-party websites that may be linked to or from the Website. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third-party websites.By using the Website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Statement. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement, please do not use the Website. We reserve the right to modify the terms of this Privacy Statement from time to time. Your continued use of the Website following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes.Information CollectedWe may collect three basic types of information about users of the Website.Information You Give Us: We receive and store information you enter on our Websites or give us in any other way, including your name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and job application.Information We Automatically Collect: We collect information about your use of our Website, such as the pages you view and other interactions you have. We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Websites. This information includes device and connection information such as statistics on your page views, traffic to and from our Website, referral URL, ad data, your IP address, and device identifiers.Information From Other Sources: We may supplement the personal information we collect with information from third parties or collected offline.Use of Your InformationWe use the information we learn about you to help us personalize and continually improve your experience using the Website. We may use your information to: (1) provide requested content; (2) personalize content on our Website; (3) send you communications about our services or special events; (4) communicate with you and respond to inquiries; (5) optimize or improve the Website and our operations; (6) detect, investigate, and prevent activities that may violate our policies or be illegal; and (7) perform statistical, demographic, and marketing analyses of users of the Website.We may also use or combine information that we collect through the Website with information that we collect about you offline to enhance, expand, and check the accuracy of our records.Sharing Your InformationWe may disclose your personal information collected via the Website to our agents, affiliates, partners, and other third parties, as described below. We may disclose information that does not specifically and personally identify you, such as aggregate information, device identifiers or other unique identifiers to third parties.Third-Party Agents and Service Providers: We have third-party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and service providers that perform functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, hosting, providing the platform used to deliver the Website, technical integration, hosting, and analytics. These entities may have access to personal information, if needed, to perform their functions.Assignment: We may change our ownership or corporate organization while providing the Website. We may also sell certain assets associated with the Website. In such event, we may transfer some or all of your information to an entity acquiring all or part of our assets or to another entity with which we have merged.Law Enforcement, Legal Process, and Emergency Situations: We may also use or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or on the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website; (2) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website or our users, or (3) act to protect the personal safety of us, users of the Website, or the public.Cookies & Tracking TechnologiesThe Website uses “cookies” to collect information about your visit and to manage your preferences. A cookie is a small computer code added to a file on your computer as a record of its visit. It does not collect or provide your personal information. It can, however, be used to note information about your visit, such as your type of web browser, operating system and Internet Protocol ("IP") address, to better tailor the Website for you. We may share information obtained from the varying kinds of cookies with third parties, including vendors, advertisers and others. You can control what cookies are accepted by your device through the settings on your browser or by deleting them. Doing so, however, may limit the personalization available to you.We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. on our Website. These analytics services uses cookies or other tracking technologies to help us analyze how users interact with and use the Website, compile reports on activity, and provide other analytical services and reports. The technologies used by these analytics services may collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, any referring website, and other information. Our Website does not use these analytics services to gather information that personally identifies you. The information generated by Google Analytics will be transmitted to and stored by Google and will be subject to Google’s privacy policies. To learn more about Google’s partner services and to learn how to opt out of tracking of analytics by Google click here.Please note that, although your device may include “Do Not Track” functionality, Instrument’s information collection and disclosure practices will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy, whether or not a Do Not Track signal is received.Opting-Out of E-Mail Marketing CommunicationsYou may always opt-out of receiving future e-mail marketing messages from Instrument. We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of such communications from us by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of each marketing e-mail. Please note that you may not opt-out of our service-related communications. Other Important InformationUsers Under Thirteen: Our Website is intended for users ages 13 and older only. Accordingly, we will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from children that we know to be under the age of 13. If we become aware of personal information in our database that was collected from a child under 13, we will delete such information.Users Outside of the United States:  If you use our Website outside of the United States, you understand and consent to the transfer of your personal information to, and the collection, processing, and storage of your personal information in, the United States and elsewhere.  The laws in the U.S. and these countries regarding personal information may be different than the laws of your state or country.Your California Privacy Rights:  If you are a California resident, California law permits you to request certain information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by us and our related companies to third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes.  To make such a request, please send your request, using the contact information listed below.If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, you should contact us by email at hello@instrument.com.All rights reserved.
